小姐，我想回家
Miss, I want to go home
好，我馬上就走，得趕一班飛機
Yeah, I'll be out here in a minute, I've got a flight to catch
找到了
That's it! I got it.
歡迎來到威奇塔中陸機場
Welcome to Wichita Mid-Continent Airport
便利、友善、價廉 歡迎搭乘
Convenient, friendly, affordable. Fly with us.
請注意，堪薩斯州清淨空氣法 規定本機場全面禁煙
Please note, the Kansas Clean Air Act has designated this airport as non-smoking.
「美國米德蘭航空飛波士頓延誤」 「美國米德蘭航空飛波士頓準時」
旅客請注意
Your attention, please. Baggage claim is located
行李提領處位於航站東側
on the east side of the terminal.
飯店暨地面交通資訊告示
Hotel and ground transportation information boards
以及公共電話位於行李轉盤的對面
and public telephones are located opposite the baggage carousels.
「你死了」
各位女士先生
Ladies and gentlemen, please maintain visual contact
請隨時留意個人物品
with your personal property at all times.
請不要留下行李或其他物品無人看管
Please do not leave your baggage or other items unattended.
感謝您的合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
-不好意思 -抱歉
-Excuse me. -Sorry.
我趕得上早一班飛機，對嗎？
So, I'm gonna make it onto the earlier flight, right?
行李要拖運嗎？
Are you gonna check that?
我會帶上機，裡面有重要東西
No, I'm gonna carry it on. It's got valuables in it.
-都辦好了 -謝謝
-Here you are. -Thank you.
-不好意思 -不，我才抱歉
-God, excuse me. -No, I'm sorry.
那個袋子重到爆
That bag is wicked heavy, anyhow.
我在看手機，我最討厭別人這麼做
I was looking at my phone. I hate it when people do that.
你沾到一點…
You have a little
髒東西
smudge.
這些是什麼？
What are these?
是龐帝克引擎用的雙腔化油器
Those are two barrel carburetors for a Pontiac Tri-Power.
那些是1974年… 雪佛蘭車款的排氣管
Those are exhaust tips for a '74 Z-28.
我專門整理舊車…
I restore old cars, so...
吹風機
Hair-dryer.
我的天，真是抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
撞上癮了
This is getting to be a habit.
是啊
Yeah, it is.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
-謝謝 -沒關係
-Thank you. -Yeah.
-謝謝 -不客氣
-Thank you. -Yeah, sure.
去波士頓？
Boston?
對
Yeah.
12號登機門
Gate 12.
一路順風，賈西亞先生
Enjoy your flight, Mr. Garcia.
謝謝
Thank you.
抱歉，您不在乘客名單上
I'm sorry. You're not on this flight.
我10分鐘前才辦好登記
Well, I just checked in for this one, like, 10 minutes ago.
一定是哪裡出錯了
That must be some sort of mistake.
抱歉，電腦顯示我們客滿了
I'm sorry, the computer shows that we're booked.
聽著，雪莉
Listen, Sharry.
明天我一手帶大的小妹要結婚
Tomorrow my little sister's getting married. I practically raised her.
抱歉，座位真的全滿了
I'm sorry, we are completely sold out.
你能幫我想想辦法嗎？我小妹耶
Listen, can you help me out for a second? She's my little sister.
她叫艾波兒，我是茱恩
She's April, I'm June,
她等著我明天陪她走紅毯
she's counting on me to march her down the aisle tomorrow.
好溫馨
That's very sweet,
搭11點50分的晚班機 您明早就會抵達
but the 11:50 will get you there tomorrow morning with plenty of time.
登機證，先生？
Your boarding pass, sir?
有時事出必有因
Sometimes things happen for a reason.
一路順風，米勒先生
Enjoy your flight, Mr. Miller.
謝謝
Thank you.
美國米德蘭航空77號班機最後登機通知
This is the final boarding call for US Midland Air, flight 77
直飛波士頓洛根機場
non-stop service to Boston's Logan Airport,
請到12號門登機
now boarding at gate 12.
持有效登機證的所有乘客請…
Would all passengers holding a valid boarding pass, please proceed...
我早該料到，他起肖到失控了
I should've seen it coming, boss. He went on tilt, he came undone.
我們這行如果失控大不了喝個幾杯
Coming undone in our business means you need a margarita.
不是在政府實驗室幹掉一票人後
It doesn't mean capping a dozen people in a government lab
再把它炸掉
and blowing it up.
不是就能竊取重大機密
It doesn't mean stealing an object of critical importance.
他到底有沒有偷走賽佛？
Does he have the Zephyr or not?
我們相信有
We believe so.
你相信有
You believe so.
看一下
Check it out.
我不在乎你相信什麼，費茲
I don't care what you believe, Fitz.
收拾好你的爛攤子
I need you to clean your mess up.
倒帶再放一次
Go back and play it again.
我要拿到賽佛
I want the Zephyr.
我們會在他抵達波士頓時拿到手
We'll have it in hand by the time he lands in Boston.
查出她的身份和背景
Find out who and what she is.
要請威奇塔的分處逮捕她嗎？
Should I have the field office pick her up in Wichita?
我有更好的主意
I got a better idea.
赫文斯小姐
Miss Havens?
我們替您找到機位了
We did find a seat for you.
請注意，抱歉延誤起飛
I'd like to have your attention, please. We apologize for the delay.
我們很快會從威奇塔機場出發
We will be departing Wichita Airport shortly.
「移動，警告」
感謝您的耐心
Thanks for your patience.
「艾瑪波拉路5826號」
我知道你只是依照公司政策做事
I know it's policy or whatever and it's just your job,
但這實在有點瞎
but it's kind of lame.
真是抱歉
Again, I apologize.
費茲，你動了什麼手腳？
Fitz. What did you do?
難怪航空公司會倒
It's no wonder these airlines are going out of business.
飛機上只有小貓兩三隻
We have been cleared onto the runway. There's nobody on the plane.
機長已開殷系好安全帶指示燈
The captain has turned on the "fasten seatbelt" sign.
請坐在位置上直到指示燈熄滅
Please remain seated until the sign has been turned off
才能在機艙內走動
and it's safe to move about the cabin.
對了，我是茱恩
I'm June, by the way.
我是羅伊米勒
I'm Roy Miller.
幸會
Nice to meet you.
彼此彼此
It's very nice to meet you.
龍舌蘭加冰塊？
Tequila on the rocks?
好，正是時候，謝了
Yeah. Just in time, thanks.
所以你小妹明天結婚？
So, your sister's getting married tomorrow?
-什麼？ -你小妹
-Excuse me? -Your sister.
她明天結婚，恭喜
She's getting married tomorrow. Congratulations.
是啊，謝了
Yeah, thanks.
羅伊，我不善於說謊
You know, Roy, I'm a bad liar.
抱歉，怎麼說？
I'm sorry, how's that?
艾波兒要結婚，不過是週六
April is getting married, but not till Saturday.
你唬到我了
You had me fooled.
可是我明天要試裝
Well, I do have a fitting tomorrow.
所以我真的得回家
So, I do, actually, have to go home.
希望這趟飛行別太難熬
I hope this isn't gonna be a rough flight.
很難說
It might be.
跑來威奇塔買化油器還真遠
Wichita is a long way to go for a carburetor.
這可不是一般的化油器
It's not just any carburetor.
是三段式化油器
It's a triple deuce.
我在整理1966年的GTO
I'm restoring a '66 GTO.
堪薩斯州有最棒的零件廠
And Kansas has the best scrap.
真的？
Really?
我爸開修車廠
My dad had a garage,
我小時候，他買了這台車的底盤
and when I was a kid, he bought this chassis.
他經常帶我們到處找零件
He used to take us to yards, and search for parts, you know?
他於1998年過世，如今艾波兒結婚
He died in '98, and now that April's getting married
我心想，何不把車整理好？
I just figured, why not finish it up,
送她當作結婚禮物
give it to her sort of as a wedding present?
也算是老爸送的禮物
Kind of like a present from our dad, too, you know?
好感人
That's nice.
-是啊 -是啊
-Yeah. -Yeah.
我常想
I used to think that
有朝一日，當最後的零件裝上
someday, when the last part went in,
我會爬進那台車，發動它
I would just climb into that GTO and start it up.
一股勁兒地開，不停地開
Just drive and drive and drive, and just keep driving
直到抵達南美洲的盡頭
until I got to the tip of South America.
合恩角
Cape Horn.
對
Yeah.
那裡有美麗的島嶼
There's beautiful islands down there.
是嗎？
Yeah?
海盜島
Pirate islands.
「有朝一日」是個危險字眼
Yeah, "someday." That's a dangerous word.
危險？
Dangerous?
它其實只是「永不」的代名詞
It's really just code for "never."
我常在想我還有什麼事沒做過
I think a lot about things I haven't done.
在大堡礁潛水，乘上東方快車
Dive in the Great Barrier Reef. Ride the Orient Express.
住在阿瑪菲海岸
Live on the Amalfi Coast
只有摩托車和背包相伴
with nothing but a motorcycle and a backpack.
在海角酒店陽台親吻陌生人
Kiss a stranger on the balcony of the Hotel Du Cap.
那在哪裡？
Where is that?
南法
South of France.
那你呢？
What about you?
你想做哪些事？
What's your list?
這個嘛…你的聽起來很不賴
Well, yours sounds pretty good.
天啊
Wow.
謝了
Thanks.
別客氣
It's no problem.
不介意的話我放在這裡
I'll just put this up here, if that's all right.
不好意思
You know what?
我要去化妝室整理一下
I'm gonna go back and use the restroom.
我幫你
I'll help you.
謝了
Thanks.
亂流真多
Lots of turbulence, huh?
-我馬上出來 -沒問題
-I'll be out in a minute. -Sure
「在海角酒店陽台親吻陌生人」
"Kiss a stranger on the balcony of the Hotel Du Cap"?
這是什麼台詞？
I mean, what kind of a line is that?
太浪漫了
I mean, it's, like, a really good line.
小姐？小姐？
Ma'am? Ma'am?
你有沒有看見他的手？
Did you see his hands, by any chance?
一下子就接住袋子
They just, like, snatched that bag right out of the air.
超快的反射動作
Lightning-fast reflexes.
太不上道
Not cool.
好
Okay.
這會有幫助
This will help.
夠了，結束了，羅伊
Enough. It's over, Roy.
我同意，夠了
Yeah, I agree. Enough.
賽佛在哪裡？
Where's the Zephyr?
那女的為什麼在機上？快說
Why is the girl on the plane? Tell me.
為什麼費茲安排她上機？
Why did Fitz put her on the plane?
別動，米勒
Don't move, Miller.
好，你打算怎麼做？ 你打算怎麼做？
So what are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
你打算讓這機會溜掉？
You're just gonna let this opportunity pass you by?
不，當然不行
No, of course you're not.
你要走出去，主動一點
You're gonna walk right through that door, you're gonna get it right.
反正你也不是第一次主動
It's not your first rodeo, woman.
嗨
Hey.
我決定也來一杯
I decided to join you.
抱歉，我…
I'm sorry. I...
不，沒關係…這樣很棒
No, no, don't... It's great.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
龍舌蘭和在高空都會令人興奮
It's just, like, the tequila and the altitude and everything.
我得告訴你一件事
There's something I've gotta tell you.
什麼？天啊，你有女朋友了
What? Oh, my God, you're in a relationship.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不是，不是那樣
No, no, no. That's not it.
不是？我洗耳恭聽，是啥？
Okay, I'm all ears. What is it?
我們要降落了嗎？
Are we landing?
還沒
No, not yet.
還沒？
No?
聽著，不需要驚慌
Listen, there's no need to panic.
我已經…控制情況
I have contained the situation.
情況？
Situation?
對，我們…失去了機長
Yeah. We've lost the pilots.
他們去哪了？
Where did they go?
應該是說他們死了
I mean, they're dead.
-機長死了 -被射殺
-The pilots are dead. -Shot. It's...
被射殺？
Shot?
誰幹的？
By who?
就是我
Well, me.
實際上我殺了正駕駛
Actually, I shot the first pilot.
他意外殺了副駕駛
He shot the second pilot accidentally.
你懂…
It's just
就是這麼回事
one of those things.
說真的，這個好笑！
Seriously, this is great!
我大可放心了，你好鎮靜
Really, I'm relieved you are taking this so well.
你要去哪裡？
Where are you going?
我去看一下，想辦法降落
I'm just gonna go check on things and think about landing.
能幫個忙繫上安全帶嗎？
Would you mind putting your seatbelt on for me?
-那就太好了 -好
-That would be great. -Yeah.
太詭異了
This is weird.
求救，求救
Mayday. Mayday.
美國米德蘭航空77號班機
This is US Midland Air 77 heavy.
這是怎麼回事？
What's happening?
機內每個人真的都死了！
Everybody's dead out there!
過來，坐下
Come on in. Sit down.
求救，求救，求救
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
這裡每個人都死了
Everybody's dead in here.
這是緊急事件
I'm declaring an emergency.
我的天啊！我們會墜機嗎？
Oh, my God! Are we going down?
什麼？
I'm sorry?
我們會墜機嗎？
Are we going down?
茱恩，只是快速下降，請坐下
No, June, it's just a rapid descent. Please, sit down.
抱歉，我想我聽夠這傢伙了
I'm sorry, I think I've heard enough of this guy.
你是飛行員嗎？你是誰？
Are you a pilot? Who are you?
肩帶
The shoulder straps.
把這個戴好
You can put those over,
從右邊扣在座位上
and it clicks in right down there.
要扣在那裡，沒錯
You wanna click it right there, that's it.
好，我弄好了
Okay, I got it, I got it. Okay...
放下起落架，慢下來
Gear down, showdown.
我們幹嘛不降落在機場？
Why can't we just land in an airport?
不，最好不要
No, no, that wouldn't be a good idea.
他們會等著我們
They'll be waiting for us.
什麼意思？等著我們？誰？
What do you mean? Waiting for us?  Who?
我想你知道愈少愈好
I think the less you know, the better.
什麼？
What?
好，我們要在這裡降落了
Okay, we're gonna touch down here.
天啊！
Oh, God. Oh, my God!
-有卡車，有卡車！ -好
-That's a truck. That's a truck! -Yeah.
-有卡車！ -沒錯
-That's a truck! -Yup.
有卡車！
That's a truck!
我的天啊！我的天啊！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-有彎路，有彎路！ -我看到了
-That's a curve. That's a curve! -I see it. I see it.
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Oh, God!
太好了
Okay, this is good.
哪裡好？
What's good?
喝一口
Take a sip of that.
可以放鬆一下
It'll take the edge off.
你中彈了？
Are you shot?
對，免騖啦
Yeah, how about that?
只是擦傷，這是好消息
It's just a scrape. That's good news.
茱恩，我們需要…
June, we have to
討論下一步
discuss what's gonna happen next.
你需要去醫院，不然去監獄？
You need to go to the hospital. Prison, maybe?
有些人會來找你，壞人
Some people are gonna come looking for you now. Bad people.
我感覺怪怪的
You know, I feel a little weird.
對，過幾分鐘你就會昏倒
Yeah, that'll pass once you fall asleep, which should be in a couple of minutes.
-什麼？ -我要你聽好
-What? -I need you to listen, June.
你對我下藥？
Did you drug me?
對
Yes.
-你對我下藥 -對，為了你著想
-You drugged me. -Yeah, it's for your own good.
這些壞人會找上你，他們會問起我
Now, look. These bad people who are going to come and see you, they're gonna ask you about me. Okay?
你得回答你不認識我
And you need to tell them you don't know me.
萊恩？
-June? June? -Okay.
你得說你什麼都不記得
You need to tell them you don't remember anything.
你無論如何要避免上他們的車
And you need to avoid getting in any vehicle with them at all costs.
好，  「他們」是誰？
Okay, who are "them"?
他們是狠角色
Well, they're serious people, June.
他們會自稱是聯邦調查局探員
They'll probably identify themselves as federal agents,
他們會誤導你
and they'll DIP you.
誤導我怎樣？
Dip me? In what?
反情報規則，他們會瞎掰我的事
Dis-Information Protocol. They'll tell you a story about me.
說我精神不穩定、有妄想症
About how I'm mentally unstable, paranoid.
暴力又危險
How I'm violent and dangerous,
聽起來都很像真的
and it'll all sound very convincing.
我已經被說服了
I'm already convinced.
一些基本的關鍵字會出現
There's a few common DIP keywords to listen for.
安慰的字眼
Reassuring words. Words like,
比如穩定、確保、安全
"stabilize," "secure," "safe."
只要他們提到這些字眼
If they say these words,
尤其重覆時…
particularly with repetition...
好
Okay.
這表示他們會殺了你
...it means they're going to kill you.
天啊！
Oh, God!
或者把你長期關到境外某處
Or intern you somewhere offshore for a very long time.
-懂嗎？ -懂
-Okay? -Okay.
仔細聽我說，只要他們說你很安全…
Now, stay with me. If they tell you you're safe...
如果他們說我很安全
If they tell me I'm safe,
他們會殺了我
they're gonna kill me.
別上什麼？
Don't get in what?
上車
Vehicles.
任何車
Any vehicles.
好，任何車
Okay, any vehicles.
-要快點逃 -我會逃
-Just run. -I'll run.
快逃-快逃
-Run. -Run.
要是他們問起我…
And if they ask you about me...
我不認識你
I don't know you.
我完全不認識你
I don't know you at all.
羅伊，你到底是誰？
Who are you, Roy?
「茱恩，很高興認識你，羅伊」
…混著雨和雪，適合滑雪區
... a mixing of rain and snow, good for ski country, but probably...
「吃頓豐盛早餐，茱恩」
-謝了，安卓 -不答氣
-Thanks, Andrea. -You're welcome.
接著回到今早的頭條新聞
Now, back to our top news story of the morning.
布萊德利摩斯在現場報導
Here's Bradley Moss, with an on-the-scene report.
根據聯邦航空局的消息 昨晚約7點半時
According to FAA sources, at approximately 7:30 last night,
與威奇塔飛往波士頓的一架客機 失去所有聯繫
all contact was lost with a Boston-bound commuter jet from Wichita.
這架飛機顯然飛經不穩定氣流
The plane was apparently passing through an area of turbulence
可能遭亂流或閃電影響
and may have met up with wind shear
造成斷電
or a lightning storm causing an electrical failure.
目前一切都還是推測
Now, this is all conjecture at this point,
證據只有… 在印地安那州玉米田中的殘骸
as all that's left is a crater in an Indiana cornfield.
來了
Coming!
「記得，別告訴任何人」
羅德尼？
Rodney?
謝天謝地，我想確定你安然無恙
Thank God. I wanted to make sure you were okay.
怎麼了？
Yeah, why?
你不是昨天從堪薩斯飛回來？
You were on that flight from Kansas, right?
-對 -我看新聞說墜機了
-Yeah. -I saw on the news about the crash.
什麼新聞？什麼墜機？
What news? What crash?
-沒事了，你活著就好 -我活著沒錯
-Anyway, you're alive. -I'm alive, yeah.
-我看到了，太好了 -茱恩，我在想…
Sure, that's cool. Hey, but, June, you know...
我告訴自己，只要得知你活著
I